[
    {
        "front": "Kochira",
        "back": "I am (here is) (Polite)",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Kochirakoso",
        "back": "Same here",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Jōzu",
        "back": "Good at\n<adj.>",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Heta",
        "back": "Not good at",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Suki",
        "back": "Like, love",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Kirai",
        "back": "Dislike",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Dewa/Ja",
        "back": "Well then",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Ginkō Kōza",
        "back": "Bank Account",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Shiryō",
        "back": "Documents",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Setsumei",
        "back": "Explanation",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Kotae",
        "back": "Answer, Reply",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Chotto",
        "back": "Little bit",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Dashimas",
        "back": "To Submit",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Mada",
        "back": "Still, yet",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Mondai ",
        "back": "Problem",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Shitsumon",
        "back": "Question",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Hoka",
        "back": "Other",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Amari",
        "back": "Not that much",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Hi",
        "back": "Day",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Madamada",
        "back": "\"not yet\"",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Empitsu",
        "back": "Pencil",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Dōshite",
        "back": "Why",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "e",
        "back": "Painting",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Kara",
        "back": "Therefore",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Zenzen",
        "back": "Not at all ",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Komakai",
        "back": "Change",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Okane",
        "back": "Money",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Ikenai",
        "back": "Can’t go",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Bansen",
        "back": "Platform",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Tsugi",
        "back": "Next",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Futsū",
        "back": "Local",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Toshokan",
        "back": "Library",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Shōgakkō",
        "back": "Primary School",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyōkai",
        "back": "Church",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Chūgakkō",
        "back": "Middle School",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Shiyakusho",
        "back": "City Hall",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Byōin",
        "back": "Hospital",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Kōshō",
        "back": "Factory",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Yūbinkyoku",
        "back": "Post Office",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Jinja",
        "back": "Temple",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Hasami",
        "back": "Scissors",
        "chapter": 8
    },
    {
        "front": "Kawa",
        "back": "River",
        "chapter": 8
    }
]